=No.9 Hunter=
=Episode 10=
Right away, sir.
May I ask
who that person is?
Even the Xuanwu Sect
treads lightly around her.
Enjoy.
She is Fengniang.
Legend says she was born deep
within the Wilds of Lize.
Her origins are a complete mystery.
She has information on everything.
Money can buy many things,
but you should never cross her.
Or she'll have you banished
from the Wilds of Lize.
Lanxi.
It's really you!
I thought I'd never see you again.
(One Month Earlier)
Lanxi.
The Stone Curse is getting worse.
If this keeps up,
you'll have to fight it back
every full moon.
Otherwise,
the Curse will consume you completely.
It is okay.
Once I find the cure,
I'll be free of this Curse for good.
No more suffering.
The cure...
We sisters have seen
countless men in Lanruo Hall.
Not once have we found
the man with your bite mark.
I'm sorry, Lanxi.
I've made you worry again.
You will be fine.
That Bitemark Man is your cure.
I will find him for you.
Listen to me.
Wherever he is,
find him,
consume him,
and live.
(Seven Days Earlier)
These Demon Essences
should be enough to get me
to Yu Linjun's Ninghua Palace.
Are you sure Yu Linjun
is the Bitemark Man you are looking for?
Would eating him really break the Curse?
My sister sent word not long ago.
She's certain the Bitemark Man
is Yu Linjun.
I wonder how your sister is doing
at the Ninghua Palace.
Godmother.
I'll bring her back.
My child,
remember this.
Never reveal that you are
the Divine Stone.
Once you reach the Palace,
watch and wait.
(To reach Ninghua Palace,)
(one must cross the Uncrossable Ferry.)
(The Ferry is swarming
with vengeful spirits.)
(No spells or powers can be used there.)
(Only a demon's body can endure it.)
(If your demon heart wavers,)
(you will perish,)
(your soul lost among the dead forever.)
Lanxi.
(A spell?)
(Lanxi.)
(Is that you?)
(Your Majesty,)
(a young demoness begs an audience.)
(She says she's the Saintess's sister.)
Where is my sister?
She kept calling your name
right up until I ate her.
She was so sweet.
And you
make my mouth water as well.
Once I feast on you,
I'll send you to join her in death.
You will pay with your life!
The Saintesses were my playthings,
my meals.
They wanted immortality,
so I gave them immortality.
But you are special.
So I'll string you up
on the Sacred Tree.
(It turns out
every ornate ornament here)
(is a girl he killed.)
I'll make you
pay with your life!
I will make all of Ninghua Palace
pay for my sister!
Miss,
I think you have the wrong person.
No, I don't.
You look exactly like my sister.
I could never mistake that.
One gold.
I was born here in the Wilds of Lize.
I've never set foot outside.
That is impossible.
How could there be such a coincidence?
Hmm.
Ask anything you want, goddess.
I may not have much else,
but I've got plenty of money.
(We are both demons.)
(You can enter my Demon Essence memory)
(and see for yourself.)
(I am not the one you seek.)
I was wrong.
It's okay.
I'm here with you.
It is all right. I am here too.
That is right. We are all here.
Sister.
I'm here.
I'm here too.
Hehehe.
Hehe.
I'm here too.
♪I drink the rain of this mortal world,
and seek the path I chose♪
♪How much sorrow and joy have I known?♪
♪With this flesh and blood,
I chase the distant light♪
♪Just to see clearly
the memories of this drifting life♪
♪Let the wind sweep away
this heavy air of sorrow♪
♪Do not forget the tangled paths
that you and I have crossed♪
♪Let towering waves come crashing down;
I'll fight against the tide♪
♪I shatter the hollow fate
they wrote for me♪
♪With a heart free of regret,
I'll face the heavens and earth♪